[{"answer": "What is that, immigrants come over, you show them how to act natural", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "No, they're not funny at all. No, I have no funny friends. I'm the funny one. my friend. Quick pan to the front door as my friend and my friend are entering", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "You see, this is what I do with women. I start out too strong, now I have to become real, that's when it all falls apart. What good is real? They don't want real, they want funny", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Ooooh, yes they do", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Oh, yes, yes, everything wonderful", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'll see you", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What mail", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Why didn't my friend pick it up", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Would you like to join us", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Oh no, it's ok, don't be silly", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "No way! It's completely under my control", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Of course I can, am I being funny now", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well thank you very much, it's about time", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Drop the case? Well, congratulations, that'll save you some money", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What's going on out there", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend?  I'll be right back", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah, the Immigration guy said his Visa was expired. Poor my friend, everything was going so well for him. He had an apartment, he had a job. What a shame", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I will, my friend! I will help you, my friend, don't worry", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What is it", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Well, you should have come to my house to pick it up", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No, actually, you're not being funny now", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Yeah, so am I being funny now", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "See, I told you I wasn't funny all the time.  Hey my friend, look, I'm not funny now", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I think it's curdled", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Do you ever laugh", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "You remember my friend", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "We try", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "We do what we can", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Comedy shows! You're a very funny man", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Oh yes, of course. TV Guide, magazines, everything. You know, I would have picked up your mail, your box is right next to mine", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "my friend, I'm gonna fix everything! I have a lawyer who knows someone in the that place, they're gonna straighten the whole thing out, the wheels are in motion, things are happening even as we speak", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "The wheels are in motion, things are happening! New scene. my friend and my friend are parked", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "What do you mean, oh boy", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Visa.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Told her the truth? Well, you got my friend deported", "qsentId": 36}]